You're gonna get off your ass
and you're gonna fly us
the fuck out of here!
If this is what you think the
country needs you to do.
then do it.
Let's talk about this
when I get back to D.C.
Where's my money?
(spits)
I don't have time for
this shit. man. Move.
- (grunts. cries)
- (inhales)
(woman screaming) Oh. my God!
Holy shit!
(gagging) What's the matter with you?
Call an ambulance!
TEDDY: You said that there was
no one here besides
you when Logan OD'ed.
Don't worry so much. Teddy Mack.
(horns honking in distance)
(stapler clicks)
(stapler clicking. siren
wailing in distance)
(stapler clicks)
(stapler clicks) JULIA: I like
this one that you started.
- (Paul babbles)
- Who's that? Is that Daddy?
- Dada.
- Oh. that's Daddy's house?
- (Paul laughs)
- You drew your house.
- We going.
- Do you wanna say hi?
Can you say. "Hi. Daddy"?
Say hi to Daddy?
- PAUL: No.
- Do you wanna show...
Do you wanna... do you wanna
tell Daddy your new word?
- (Paul babbles. laughs)
- (laughs)
Yeah! (Gasps)
- Oh. you're a good boy.
- (babbles)
Oh...
- Can you say...
- (babbles)
Oh. Almost. You ready? I'm
gonna throw it to you now.
- Ready for the ball?
- Ready!
Oh! (Laughs)
(Paul giggles. squealing)
(bottle cap clatters)
(laughing) He fell over.
- But I caught it.
- (babbles)
That was such a good catch!
Can you throw it back to Mommy?
(Paul babbles) (telephone
buttons beeping)
- Hey! (Laughs)
- I drop it!
What about this? You wanna
keep drawing with me?
(recording stops. line rings)
(line connects) Hello?
Hey. How's the head?
I'll never complain
about a migraine again.
How'd it go with Avi?
Ah. it was fine. (Sighs)
Wish I could say the
same for the Mexicans.
What happened?
Lucia didn't have the money.
Puta madre.
I gave her 48 hours
to come up with it.
but I don't trust she's
gonna come through.
So I need you to start
looking for another buyer.
(sighs) Why can't you do it?
Because I am going to D.C..
and then to San
Antonio to make sure
that the guns get
to the Contras.
You remember what I told you
about me not being
a drug dealer?
All right. the sooner
we get the money.
the sooner we can get the
supplies to your people.
So just do what you can. okay?
I'll see you in a day or two.
Bye. (line disconnects)
(sighs)
♪♪
(speaks indistinctly)
She probably... Oh. my God.
CLAUDIA: Right
there. right there.
KEVIN: How old is she again? LEON:
Who gives a shit? She fine.
- Hey. I'd hit that.
- After I finish. nigga.
- I'm-a smack that shit up.
- Man. she is fine.
That thing... I'm-a smack it.
What is wrong with you two?
Claudia.
Meet Leon Simmons and Kevin
Hamilton. my business partners.
Is there a Big Brother Big
Sister meetin' around here
I don't know about? (laughs)
Um. FKL Incorporated at
your service. ma'am.
Nigga. no. FLK Incorporated.
- Since when?
- Nigga. you just got here.
Take these clowns back
to the circus. please.
What you say. lady?
We about business.
Look. lil' nigga. the
only business you about.
you pick up a rag and start
polishing wood. (Scoffs)
Otherwise. I need you
and your butt boy
to get the fuck out of here.
Did she just...
I'll handle it. man.
It's all good.
Y'all getting paid either way.
Busted old bitch!
Forget her. Come on.
She don't know who
she talkin' to.
(door creaks open)
I thought you was
serious. young blood.
(door closes) I am.
(unzips bag)
I just need folks I can trust.
You know what a cliché is?
Uh-huh.
Well. I'm gonna hit you
with one right now.
The stuff you dealing in.
ain't nobody you can trust.
I'm only taking two.
Well. I've got four.
and they all pure.
I told you. I am a
purveyor of entertainment.
not a drug dealer.
Okay.
You know anybody who
might be interested?
No. Franklin. I do not know
anybody who'd be interested.
Didn't you learn anything in your
encounter with Lenny and Ray-Ray?
You're gonna have to get your
dead presidents someplace else.
You stick around
these four blocks.
you bound to catch fire.
Another cliché?
A prophecy.
You like that?
If you ever want me to
teach you something.
you just come on
back through. 'kay?
Till then. beat it. I'm busy.
It's like when the X-Men went
up against the Hellfire Club.
How the hell they know
how it's gonna go down?
Jean Gray fucked 'em over.
And all Mastermind had to do to
get her to be the Black Queen
was get inside her head.
You do that to a trick.
you'll have her forever.
What the fuck is
you talking about?
I thought you liked Phoenix.
No one ever really
liked Phoenix.
Her soul was corrupted.
Look at this here.
Bitch-ass niggas out
here. three for one.
(clip clicks) Out here slippin'.
Hey. you sure you
wanna take it there?
I mean. we robbed them.
and they got us back.
Maybe we could let
this shit slide...
Hey. niggas broke into my spot.
Tied me up and hit me with a
motherfucking baseball bat.
And you talkin' 'bout letting
that shit ride. nigga?
What the fuck wrong with you?
Okay. I'm ready.
- You rollin'. nigga?
- I'm ready.
- You ready. nigga?
- What?
Roll your window down.
(switch rattles)
What the fuck's wrong
with the window. man?
(rattles)
It's not fucking opening. I
need to roll the window down.
(ignition alert dinging)
Is there a problem?
Don't know.
- What you boys doing here?
- Nothin'.
We just cruisin'.
Then cruise.
I know you don't
live around here.
So move along.
or I can start my day off
right by making an arrest.
Let's go. man.
(window whirring)
RAY-RAY: Come on. man.
(engine starts)
(indistinct conversation)
(laughs)
All right.
♪♪
- My mom not home. too.
- I know. I dropped her off.
- I can't wait to see this money.
- You stupid.
- (laughs)
- (exhales deeply)
(deadbolt clicks)
♪♪
(curtain rings swoosh)
- Whoo! Hoo-hoo!
- (laughs)
Oh. my God!
(laughter)
Whoo! Hoo-hoo!
Oh. yeah! (Laughs)
- Get that shit. Get that shit.
- (speaks indistinctly)
We rich! (Laughs)
Hey. Who your daddy?
Who's your daddy?
What you call that bird? Melody?
Man. shut up. man.
You know you want that
doughnut-eater's daughter.
Ah.
And he got his shoes on my bed!
- (Leon laughs)
- You can buy a new bed.
Keep her name out your mouth.
- Get your own Melody.
- (laughs)
KEVIN: Damn. nigga! (Laughs)
- Hey. you ever done it before?
- What? With Melody?
No. get your head out
of her ass. man.
I'm talking about
this nose candy.
Nah. man. that's the
cardinal rule...
Don't get high on your own supply.
Motherfucker.
how we supposed to sell it if
we don't know what it's like?
Exactly. People who buy coke know
what it feel like. dumb-ass.
Now stop messing around and
help me cut this shit.
- (laughs)
- Man. cut it yourself.
Get your shoes off my bed. man.
I'm talking about
this stupid bed. man.
(speaks indistinctly) (laughter)
FRANKLIN: Careful
with that shit. man.
Hey. so you said
3/4's cocaine and...
1/4 baby formula. right? Uh-huh.
Yeah. how you know that?
The Israeli. (dog
barking in distance)
Hey. so how many of these bags
you supposed to be making?
As many as we can.
Probably go a little faster we
had some powder to help us out.
KEVIN: Mm-hmm. Claudia right
about y'all two. man. huh?
You a couple clowns
or you businessmen?
We a couple of clowns. fool.
(laughs) (knocking
on front door)
- Oh. shit.
- Shit.
Hide the shit and keep quiet.
I got this.
No. no. no. You crazy?
Don't answer it.
- I'm-a just see who it is.
- Hey. hey. man.
How we supposed to hide this?
Figure it out.
Shit! I got the money.
I got the money.
(knock on front door) Fuck!
(dog barking in distance.
children shouting playfully)
(Leon and Kevin
speaking indistinctly)
(clatter)
LEON: Let's get to work.
Oh. man. Uh. shit.
It's only Mel. man.
We was just talking about you.
(Leon and Kevin laugh)
Man. crazy. Hey. y'all... y'all
trippin'. man. It's just Melly Mel.
- How you doin'. girl?
- MELODY: What y'all doing?
- (exhales deeply)
- Damn!
Great fucking hiding job!
- I want some!
- LEON: Listen to your girl. man.
That's what I was saying.
For the last time. ain't
nobody doing this damn coke!
- Damn!
- You gonna sell it?
- 'Cause I can help you sell it.
- You're not helping. Mel.
We need to go back to
the Volpes. all right?
They got titties all
over the place.
and your friend's
mom is fine. too.
I saw half her pussy
the last time.
- Which half?
- Volpes already got enough coke.
And I ain't nickel-and-diming
in the Valley.
- That's how you get arrested.
- All right. all right.
What about. like. Bel
Air or some shit?
Ah-ah! I heard folks
up there got coin.
You wanna go
door-to-door in Bel Air
like we selling candy bars? KEVIN:
I don't know why y'all trippin'.
I told y'all I got a cousin
named Devon up in Oakland.
He got a gang of connections.
We could take a road trip.
- Road trip?
- Yeah. Hell. yeah.
Right? You wanna go on a
road trip. Melly Mel?
- (chuckles) Maybe.
- Yeah?
- Y'all are sounding crazy.
- Y'all did some. didn't you?
- No. (Sniffs)
- (laughs)
(stifles laugh)
Get your black asses
out my house.
- Hey. man.
- Hey. what'd it feel like?
- Ah. man. I can't even...
- Franklin. this shit's amazing!
- I can't believe you.
- It's...
- Come on. man.
- Hey. man! Hold up!
Where you gonna
sell this shit at?
- Once I figure that out...
- Hey!
And y'all two fools sober up...
Why I gotta leave?!
I'll let y'all know.
Because I got shit to do.
- Hey. come on. man.
- Things I gotta do.
- MELODY: Dang.
- FRANKLIN: Man. get out.
Let's go find a pool
or something. man.
Hey. man. I wanna swim.
Don't y'all wanna swim?
You don't know how to swim. Man.
of course I know how to swim.
Hey. you know. you look so good in
bikinis... I'll take that. thank you.
- Thanks. man.
- You're welcome.
- KEVIN: Hey.
- MELODY: Come on.
Come on. man. Hey. don't
shut us out. Hey!
(woman speaking
indistinctly over PA)
How many of these places
do you wanna check?
As many as we have to.
He might be dead already.
(telephone ringing in distance)
(sighs) So you know
him from Texas?
Mm-hmm.
From foster care.
We came to L.A. together.
Why didn't you guys
keep in touch?
(speaks Spanish)
(monitor beeping steadily.
telephone ringing)
(man coughing)
(indistinct conversations)
Hernan.
(machine whooshing)
(speaking Spanish)
What the fuck are
you doing here?
Looking for you. ese.
I wanna talk to you.
- You brought your girlfriend?
- Business partner. Lucia.
Nice to meet you.
I don't know what kind of
business you got with Gustavo.
but watch your back.
He tends to run when
things get scary.
Right. vato?
How you doing. Hernan?
(monitor beeps)
I don't know yet.
(woman speaking
indistinctly over PA)
Any gang in the city would kill
to have access to our product.
Why the fuck you talking to
me like you know me. jaina?
Hey. man. all we're asking
for is an introduction.
Those guys out there.
they're my brothers now.
I say the word. and they bash
both your fucking heads in.
They're gonna pay
your bills. too?
Hmm?
They're gonna look after
Nuvia and the children
once you're gone?
With dialysis. you live. what?
Five years?
LUCIA: My aunt
lasted maybe three.
(whispers) Right?
You can't afford not
to help us. ese.
What are you offering?
(sighs)
A cut from everything
Los Monarcas buy.
(whispers) Set up the meet.
And if Stomper tells you
to go fuck yourself?
Then we'll give you a
half-ounce of blow.
Just for your trouble.
I owe you. vato.
I owe you. Let me pay you back.
Órale.
TEDDY: So the guns are
being held up at the depot
by this mid-level
prick who thinks
he isn't getting enough
respect from the Contras.
I'm sure the
Ambassador just wants
to be taken into consideration.
Okay. well. while he's
waiting for his ego
to be properly stroked. our
guys are dying down there.
It'll take some time to smooth
it over with the prick.
How much time?
You really want another Bay
of Pigs on your hands?
I thought you had
this under control.
- I do.
- And yet. here we are.
Look. I just need a little push.
Be nice if it came from the top.
Looks like you had some
trouble in Honduras.
I-I don't... What
does that mean?
Do you need someone else
working with you on this?
No.
I-I already have somebody.
He's a Nicaraguan national.
He's military-trained.
He knows what the stakes are.
Okay. here's the progress
report for the President.
The Contras will have everything
they need once they get those guns.
(chuckles)
You say that again.
and you'll spend the rest of
your career behind a desk.
Maybe I can go around
the Ambassador.
hit up a buddy at the depot.
might expedite things.
I'd appreciate that.
You look like shit. Teddy.
I appreciate that. too.
I hope I haven't made
a mistake with you.
You haven't.
(line rings)
(telephone rings)
(coughs)
(ring) (Paul babbling)
- Hello?
- TEDDY: Hey. It's me.
Hi.
Yeah. I. uh.
I tried the office. They
said that you were home.
(babbling)
Sorry. (Clears throat)
Were we supposed to talk today?
(telephone clatters)
Wh... No. I'm here. I'm...
I'm in D.C.
- I landed this afternoon.
- Oh.
You know. I-I had a-a
meeting with James.
but also I was. uh. I was
hoping I could see you.
About?
Okay. Um...
You know. I've... I've been
doing a lot of thinking.
Um...
soul searching or whatever.
Look. I-I haven't stopped
thinking about you guys
since you were in Los Angeles.
And. um. I want us
to be together.
- And I miss you and...
- Teddy. stop.
- No. just hear me out. please.
- Stop.
Give me that much. at least.
You know. I-I could've just
shown up at your door.
but I'm trying to do
this the right way.
Please.
Julia.
If you come over.
I don't want any bullshit.
Yeah.
And I don't know if I
want us to be together.
I understand.
I want Thai food.
I'll see you at 8.
♪♪
(receiver clatters)
JEROME: Hey.
Mmm! Yeah. baby.
(13th Amendment's The
Stretch playing)
(chuckles)
Unh. Toll House.
How many you want?
- Uh. two.
- Ooh!
Thanks.
Ah. (Chuckles)
(cookie clatters) Yeah.
A man gotta know how to survive.
Louie leave me. I
know how to eat.
(laughs)
Why you laughing?
(dog barking in distance)
Um...
(bills rustle)
For the gun.
- Oh. yeah?
- Mm.
Something tell me this more
than the reason why you here.
I mean. I'm...
I know you don't want in
on the coke business.
I just wanna know why.
I-I mean. you
smart. plenty hard.
Hmm.
And I know you like that paper.
So if you ain't in the game.
there's gotta be a good reason.
About 18 months ago.
some niggas jacked this
Mexican diesel truck.
(mouth full) Full of cocaine.
Before that. we were somewhat
a'ight with the Mexicans.
And a lot of people got tapped behind
that situation. (Beads rattle)
And that's the first reason
I don't fuck with no yeyo.
Rule number two. 'cause
there ain't no winners.
Them pigs. they ready to
put you in the clink.
- And... and they will.
- Mm-hmm.
Now rule number three.
you gotta sell to white folk.
Them places where
you gon' stick out.
target on your back.
(lighter clicks) That's right.
(chuckles)
There's gotta be a
way I can do this
without ending up
dead or in jail.
(exhales) Only way
you can make it safe
is selling right here.
in your own hood.
Just like I do with my bud.
They can't afford no blow.
Take him to Knees'.
Who?
Better he hear it from somebody
who ain't related to him.
Go and wait out in the car.
Go on. I'll be out
there in a minute.
- (speaks indistinctly)
- What? I'm sayin'...
(beads rattle. door opens)
Appreciate you handling with me.
Mm-hmm.
You sure did change
your tune real quick.
What you got up your sleeve?
Nothin'. What you got up yours?
Mm. Mmm!
Look like he ain't the
only one with a hard head.
You know. if he put his
mind on something.
it's gonna be tough to
get him off. right?
Yeah.
I gotta go.
(clatter)
(panting. moaning)
(Paul crying)
It's okay. Keep going.
(grunting)
(moaning)
(both grunt and moan)
Oh! Oh. shit.
(clatter) Oh. shit.
(both moan)
(breathing heavily)
Oh. my God. I've missed that.
I gotta check on Paul.
(Paul crying)
Oh.
(breathing heavily)
(Paul wailing)
Oh. shit.
(wailing continues)
Okay.
So... what's changed?
(clears throat) I mean.
clearly. something's happened.
Trust me. You don't
want the details.
I said no bullshit.
Okay. look.
I know I can be difficult. um.
controlling. myopic.
Holy shit. should I
be writing this down?
Okay. I'm admitting
that you were right.
that maybe it's better if
I can put some distance
between myself and the op.
What kind of distance?
Look. I finish getting
everything set up.
I let Alejandro run point.
and then I oversee the
whole operation from here.
You think you can do that?
Yeah. I'm in charge. I
can do whatever I want.
I don't mean are you
allowed to do it.
I mean...
can you. Teddy E. MacDonald.
are you capable of doing that?
Yes.
Yes. if it means
being here with you?
Yes.
I mean. come on. I'm dying here.
Be great if you were here.
You know. a week ago. you
seemed pretty intent
on being out front
on this thing.
Just. I mean. look...
A lot's happened
in the last week.
but. you know. this is
just the next step.
I need assurances. which means
no half-truths. no hiding.
Yes. I promise. I promise.
I call. you pick up.
And if you change your mind...
That's not... that's not
gonna happen. okay?
Listen. I hear you.
I'm not gonna spend the
next 10 years of my life
hanging my heart
and my son's heart
on your whims. Okay. our son.
I'm giving you one
more shot. Teddy.
Don't screw it up.
♪♪
(VCR whirs)
The '50s. we had clubs.
not gangs. like the
crazy kids nowadays.
Back then. we had clubs
to protect the neighborhood
from the spook hunters.
Bunch of crazy-ass crackers
trying to kill us.
They won that fight. though.
(sighs deeply)
By the end of the '60s.
whitey had flown away.
and the hood was ours. Knees...
we ain't here for
no history lesson.
Young blood needs context.
Hand me them darts. man.
From '65 to '70.
there were no black
gangs in L.A.
We were all too busy protesting.
We had purpose.
But when the FBI...
(dart clacks)
Infiltrated y'all. it
destroyed the movement.
My Pop's a Panther.
(shouting in Korean)
(Jerome laughs)
(speaking Korean)
(laughs)
(mutters in Korean)
(lighter clicks)
Fuck you. Knees!
(grunts)
(door slams)
I thought you got a divorce.
(inhales deeply)
Activism doesn't pay. (sighs)
And them Korean soaps be
selling like hotcakes.
Look. man. we ain't
got all day. huh?
I need you to tell little
man the real deal.
Tell him how you lost a nut.
Yeah.
A coke deal went all wrong.
Mexicans had my
homeboy on his knees
in front of my nutsack.
Bullet went straight through.
So you be careful what
you're playing with. boy.
Told you. They run the
whole cocaine flow.
One gang does.
I straightened out
after I lost my nut.
All my dealings are
on the level now.
What gang?
(Jerome laughs)
What does it matter?
You fucking with
that white girl?
That coke life?
One nut be about the best
scenario you can expect.
(scale clicks)
(sighs) That's 14 kilos.
3 ounces. 4 grams.
(inhales deeply. exhales slowly)
(speaking Spanish)
And what are the chances
your boy. uh...
Hernan is actually just setting
us up to be robbed and killed?
Oh...
50/50.
(chuckles) Perfecto.
(exhales deeply)
Any word from Pedro?
No. He's probably on a bender.
Better keep an eye on him.
(cap tightens on bottle) Well.
I don't even wanna see him.
(sighs)
What do you do for fun?
This. (chuckles)
And what? Eat patas
de mula like my dad?
Work out?
Jerk off?
(siren wailing in distance)
(sighs) Salud.
(glass clatters)
(coughs)
(chuckling)
(exhales deeply)
Now. uh... (glasses clatter)
Are you gonna tell me what happened...
(coughs)
between you and Hernan?
(sniffles)
(whispers) No.
(liquor pours)
(button clicks)
(exhales deeply)
(Los Solitarios' Mi Amor
Es Para Ti playing)
(glasses clink)
(laughs) (glass clatters)
(exhales sharply)
(coughing)
(laughs)
Ohh.
Eh... (speaks Spanish)
♪♪
(both laughing)
(horn honks in distance)
(vehicle passes)
(indistinct conversations)
(Muzak playing.
toaster clicking)
(toaster button clicks)
Well. I figured I hadn't
seen the last of you.
You want one?
No. thank you.
I wanna know where...
I know what you want.
But even if I told you
where to find them.
they ain't gonna
talk to your ass.
How much you want
for an address?
(crunching)
(pen clicks)
(sighs)
You get three jewels
in this life. son...
What your mama tells you.
what these streets teach you.
and what the future holds.
which nobody knows.
♪♪
It's the last one you
got control over.
(scribbling)
You gotta ask yourself
one question.
(pen clicks)
"Who's gonna own my life when
it's all said and done?"
My uncle ain't here. man. You
don't have to lecture me.
You ain't grown enough to know
good advice when you hear it.
(paper rips)
(pad thuds) That gold nugget...
(pen thuds)
that was free.
This here?
Cost you a G.
(Grupo Celeste's
Como Un Ave playing)
(indistinct conversations)
(inhales sharply)
(music continues in distance)
(clicking teeth)
(rooster crowing in distance)
- (woman speaks indistinctly)
- Not bad.
LUCIA: It's pure. Stomper.
For this kind of product.
you can charge a lot more.
We know you're expanding
territory. vato.
Can get you as much as you need.
We get our shit through
other channels.
Well. see. they're
ripping you off. ese.
We're not affiliated
with any cartel.
And we deliver the
product right to you.
No more TJ pickups or drop-offs.
Less risk.
You vouch for them
like that. vato?
(dog barking in distance)
I trust 'em enough
to bring 'em here.
Hey. Does she come with the deal?
Huh?
'Cause I like me a
little Chicanita.
(laughter)
Hey. hey. (Sniffs)
I'm Memo.
Little Chicanita.
(laughter) MAN: Whoo-hoo!
(sniffs. laughs)
(speaking Spanish)
Ooh. (Speaking Spanish)
What comes in here...
Ah. is mine. (Laughs)
Memo. shut the fuck up.
Hey. but we look so
good together. huh?
Lay the fuck off her. pendejo.
(all murmur)
He just looks mad. Stomper. huh?
He wants to fight me. (laughter)
You're a wrestler. right?
Not anymore. I'm here
to talk business.
When I'm done with you. ese.
you're not gonna be able to talk.
MAN: Whoo!
It looks like whether you got any
fucking balls... (inhales deeply)
is the business at hand.
- (man laughs)
STOMPER: Huh? WOMAN: Yeah!
- Okay!
- MAN: Yeah!
(shouting in Spanish)
(indistinct conversations
in Spanish)
(speaks Spanish)
Oso...
Beat his ass.
I'd rather die than get fucked
by one of these marranos.
(indistinct conversations
in Spanish continue)
♪♪
(vacuum whirring)
Hey. Mom.
(loudly) Hey. Mama! Hey!
What you got there?
(vacuum turns off) Snacks for you and
the fine ladies of the Spades Club.
Ooh!
(beads rattling)
You got money.
Got a job. Hey.
Working for the Volpes.
(laughs) What. you're fluffin'?
Aw. damn. Mom. come on.
It's just a production.
For porn shoots.
You spending nights there again?
No. I'm just coming home late.
Well. I guess it's a paycheck.
Think I could take the
car for a few hours?
Oh. now I see what's happening.
I'll get the oil changed.
Huh? Uh-huh.
And a wash. Mm-hmm.
You know that car dirty.
(keys jangle)
Fine. (kisses)
Love you. Go.
Love you. love you. Best in the world.
(keys jangle)
Come back for dinner. okay?
I'll be there.
All right.
(door creaking)
(dog barking in distance)
(unlocks car door)
(car door creaks)
(rooster crows)
(indistinct shouting)
(grunting)
(indistinct shouting continues)
(punches landing.
grunting continues)
(shouting continues)
(laughs)
(rooster crows)
(speaks Spanish)
(speaks Spanish) (inhales)
(shouts in Spanish)
(all shouting in Spanish)
(grunts)
ALL: Oh!
(shouts in Spanish)
(grunting)
CROWD: Ohh!
(crowd shouting indistinctly)
- (shouts in Spanish)
- Oso.
(breathing heavily)
(liquor sloshes)
(spits. exhales sharply)
How much?
(breathing heavily)
19 per key.
And we need to talk protocol.
And then we celebrate.
(rooster crows)
MAN: Let's do it!
(cheers and applause)
(man hooting)
(indistinct conversations
in Spanish)
Get up. Memo. (speaks Spanish)
When will they be delivered?
By the end of the week.
Why so long?
It's a CIA-run weapons facility.
Why would there be delays?
Because people's egos
have to be entertained.
Ah. Whose egos?
I don't know. man. Don't worry.
(sighs)
Next time. I'll fly
you. if you want.
You'd rather fly me
across the country
than pick me up at
LAX. wouldn't you?
Absolutely.
You have any luck finding
another buyer for the coke?
Not yet.
That's okay. We'll
figure it out.
Hey. pull over up here.
I'm fucking starving.
(turn signal clicks)
(under breath) 23. 23.
♪♪
(indistinct conversations
in Spanish)
(gears shift. engine turns off)
♪♪
(knocks) (chuckles)
You lost? Huh?
Who you looking for?
No one.
Oh. you must be
looking for someone.
You stopped right here.
Nah. I think I'm on
the wrong street.
Why you nervous?
I'm just gonna head out.
Hold up. man.
You got a name?
Franklin.
Godspeed. Franklin.
(engine starts)
(gears shift)
(glass shatters)
(grunting)
Yeah. yeah. you in the wrong
fucking street. all right.
You strapped? Huh? No. man.
I-I just wanna offer you
the product I'm selling.
I'm not here to
start any trouble.
(groans) Bullshit!
Please. man!
(groans) Get the fuck off me!
(indistinct shouting)
You're making a mistake. man!
I'm not fucking...
I promise you. man! (gun cocks)
You're making a mistake. man!
(grunting)
Take him up in the house.
(speaks Spanish)
That's my jaina's goddaughter. vato.
Get him upstairs now.
I don't want any trouble. man!
I'm just here to offer you the
product I'm selling. man!
I-I don't want any fucking trouble!
Come on. man!
I'm telling you the truth. man.
I can explain everything.
Shut the fuck up. man!
You're making a mistake. man!
I'm just here to sell
my product. man!
I-I'm here to offer you my product!
Oso.
Oso. vente.
Oso. I can explain
all of this. man.
Wait. what?
Man. who the fuck are you?
(panting) (dog
barking in distance)
What did he do?
He's a mayate in the wrong
fucking neighborhood.
Maybe he came here to smoke us.
No. man. (Inhales sharply)
He had this.
And I don't answer to you.
so get the fuck outta here.
I know this vato.
He's coming with me.
(laughs) I don't give a fuck...
(whistles)
You show your face here
again. you a dead man.
(panting) You got a car?
Hmm? Huh?
You got a fucking car?
(continues panting)
Hey. you okay?
What? You okay?
What you doing here. Oso? Huh?
You need to go. okay?
I remember you. too.
Hey. you need to go.
Órale.
(speaks Spanish)
(rooster crows)
(speaks Spanish) Sí.
Oh. wait. I'm Franklin.
I'm Franklin Saint.
Y-you ever need anything.
you come find me.
Okay. Franklin Saint. Get
the fuck out of here.
Órale.
(car door closes)
(The Temptations' Smiling
Faces Sometimes plays)
(brakes squeal)
What?
You know her?
Yes.
Well. how?
She's one of the girls I killed.
(keys jangle)
(door bangs open)
♪ Smiling faces
♪ Sometimes pretend
♪ To be your friend
♪ Smiling faces show no traces ♪
♪ Of the evil that
lurks within ♪
♪ Smiling faces
♪ Smiling faces sometimes
♪ They don't tell the truth
♪ Smiling faces. smiling faces ♪
♪ Tell lies and I got proof
♪♪